Salvador Luria Papers 1923-1992 Mss.Ms.Coll.39
American Philosophical Society
- Series IV. Works by others, 1944-1990; 11 linear feet
  - "An Acidic pH Requirement for Insertion of Colicin E1 into Artificial Membrane Vesicles: Relevance to the Mechanism of Action of Colicins, Toxins, and Viral Proteins", [1984]; Cramer, William A.; Davidson, Victor L. (Box 53)
  - Prediction of Bilayer Spanning Domains of Hydrophobic and Amphipathic Membrane Proteins: Application to the Cytochrome b and Colicin Families, Cramer, William A.; Peterson, A.A.; Shiver, J.W.; Widger, W.R. (Box 53)
  - Some Properties of the Colicin E1 Immunity Protein, n.d.; Bishop, Lauren J.; Cramer, William A.; Davidson, Victor L. (Box 53)
  - Sociology of Science: Biliography, 1971; Crane, Diane (Box 53)
  - "Some Physical, Chemical and Geometrical Principles Which Underlie the Problem of Biological Growth", Crane, H.R. (Box 53)
  - Some Footnotes on Protein Synthesis: A Note for the RNA Tie Club, Dec. 1959; Brenner, Sydney; Crick, F[rancis] H.C. and S. Brenner; Crick, Francis, 1916-2004 (Box 53)
  - UV-Induced Genetic Recombination in a Partially Diploid Strain of Escherichia Coli, 1967; Curtiss, Roy III (Box 54)
  - The Control of Development in Temperate Bacteriophages. II. Control of Lysozyme Synthesis, n.d.; Couturier, Marcel A. J., 1897-; Dambly, C.; Thomas, R. (Box 54)
  - Current Views on the Reproduction of Bacteriophages, n.d.; Delbrück, Max (Box 54)
  - The Mechanism of Genetic Recombination in Phage, n.d.; Delbrück, Max and N. Visconti (Box 54)
  - Problems of Modern Biology in Relation to Atomic Physics: A Series of Lectures, 1944; Delbrück, Max (Box 54)
  - Delbrück, Max (Box 54)
    Reports
    - 1950-1955, Folder #1 (Box 54)
    - 1956-1960, n.d., Folder #2 (Box 54)
  - Virology Revisited--Lecture, 17 Oct. 1976; Delbrück, Max (Box 54)
  - The Production of Noninfectious Viral Components in Bacteria Infected with Bacteriophage, 1953; DeMars, Robert Ivan (Box 54)
  - A Proposal for a Uniform Nomenclature in Bacterial Genetics, 1966; Adelberg, Edward A; Clark, Alvin J.; Demerec, M., (Milislav), 1895-1966; Hartman, Philip E. (Box 54)
  - "Specialized Nucleoprotein Structures at the Origin of Replication of Bacteriophage L: Complexes with L O Protein and with L O, L P, and E. Coli dnaB", Dodson, Mark; Echols, Harrison; McMacken, Roger; Roberts, John (Box 54)
  - A Consideration of Virus-Host Relationship in Virus-Induced Neoplasia at the Cellular Level, Dulbecco, Renato, 1914- (Box 54)
  - "Material for President's Report, 1953-1954", Dulbecco, Renato, 1914- (Box 54)
  - Report, n.d.; Dulbecco, Renato, 1914- (Box 54)
  - Summaries of the Fifth Seminar on Animal Cells and Animal Viruses, 1959; Dulbecco, Renato, 1914- (Box 54)
  - Mutagenizing Experiments and Serratia Marcescens Experiments, 1962-1963; Dushman, Miriam B. (Box 55)
  - The Origin of Prototrophic Variants in Mixtures of Auxotrophic Mutants of Serratia Marcescens, [1963]; Dushman, Miriam B. (Box 55)
  - PII Experiments, 1963-1964; Dushman, Miriam B. (Box 55)
  - Streptomycin Resistance and Dependence and Its Controlling Mechanisms, Dushman, Miriam B. (Box 55)
  - The Rolling Circle for ØX DNA Replication. II. Synthesis of Single-Stranded Circles, Dressler, David (Box 55)
  - The Expression of the Galactose Locus in Transductional Heterogenotes of Escherichia Coli K-12, n.d.; Cederbaum, Stephen; Ebisuzaki, Kaney (Box 55)
  - Studies on UV Sensitive Mutants of Bacteriophage T4: Gene Selectivity, [1965]; Ebisuzaki, Kaney (Box 55)
  - A Test of an Hypothesis Concerning Ultraviolet Irradiation Damage and Phage Functions, Ebisuzaki, Kaney (Box 55)
  - The Regulation of Viral Genes and the Uncontrolled Expression of the Galactose Genes During L Development, Butler, B.; Echols, Harrison; Joyner, A. (Box 55)
  - High Negative Interference and Heterozygosis: A Study on the Mechanism of Recombination in Bacteriophage T4, Edgar, Robert S. (Box 55)
  - Phenotypic Properties of Heterozygotes in the Bacteriophage T4, n.d.; Edgar, Robert S. (Box 55)
  - "Progress Report: January 1 to December 31, 1962", Edgar, Robert S. (Box 55)
  - Temperature Sensitive Mutants of T4D, n.d.; Edgar, [Robert S.], Sussman, and Gordan; Edgar, Robert S.; Sussman (Box 55)
  - Gene Regulation During Viral Development, Aug. 1964; Edlin, Gordan (Box 55)
  - "Comparative Micromorphology of Normal, Transforming, and Malignant Cells", Mar. 1960; Edwards, George A. (Box 55)
  - Genetics and Physiology of Defective Lysogeny in E. Coli K12 (L): Studies of Early Mutants, Eisen, H.A., C.R. Fuerst, and L. Siminovitch; Eisen, Herman; Fuerst, Clarence R.; Siminovitch, Louis (Box 55)
  - The Human Nature of Human Nature, 1 Oct. 1971; Eisenberg, Leon (Box 55)
  - Molecular Basis for the Action of Macrocyclic Antibiotics on Membranes, n.d.; Ciani, S.M.; Eisenman, G.; McLaughlin, S.G.A.; Szabo, G. (Box 56)
  - Constitution of Tumor Viruses, Mar. 1960; Epstein, M.A. (Box 56)
  - Escape from Repression in Phage-Carried lac Genes, 1967; Epstein, Wolfgang (Box 56)
  - A Study of Multiplicity-Reactivation in the Bacteriophage T4, 1957; Epstein, Richard H. (Box 56)
  - Effect of DNA Structure and Nucleotide Sequence on Holliday Junction Resolution by a Saccharomyces Cerevisiae Endonuclease, 1987; Evans, David H.; Kolodner, Richard (Box 56)
  - An Episomic Element in a Strain of Salmonella Typhosa, [1962]; Baron, Louis S.; Falkow, Stanley (Box 56)
  - Molecular Studies of Episomic Elements, n.d.; Falkow, Stanley (Box 56)
  - Deletion of 43 Aminoacids in the N-Terminal Half of the Large Tumor Antigen of Simian Virus 40 Results in a Non-Karyophilic Protein Capable of Transforming Established Cells, [1984]; Fischer Fantuzzi, Lia; Vesco, Cesare (Box 56)
  - Integration of L and Lb2 Genomes in Non-Immune Host Bacteria Carrying a L Cryptic Prophage, [1967]; Fischer-Fantuzzi, L[ia] (Box 56)
  - Lysogenication of Bacteria Carrying L cry Prophage, n.d.; Fischer Fantuzzi, Lia; Kabat, Jonathan P. (Box 56)
  - Production and Isolation of Mutants of Bacillus Subtilis, Jun. 1950; Fisher, Earl, Jr. (Box 56)
  - Bang You're Dead (Some Reflections on the Art of Survival), 11 Oct. 1961; Fowlie, Alfred H., Jr. (Box 56)
  - On the Mechanism of Deoxyribonucleate Integration in Pneumococcal Transformation, 1964; Allen, Marcia K.; Fox, Maurice Sanford (Box 56)
  - Physical and Genetic Hybrids Formed in Bacterial Transformation, Fox, Maurice Sanford; Gurney, Theodore, Jr. (Box 56)
  - Recombination Within a Gene Is by Conversion, n.d.; [Fox] (Box 56)
  - [Experiment Notes], 1954; Fraser, Dorothy (Box 56)
  - Fragmentation of L Prophage After Induction, [1967]; Fraser, Dorothy (Box 56)
    -See also Ser.I, Fraser, Dorothy
    -See also Ser.I, Signer, Ethan R.
  - The Molecular Mechanisms of Mutations, Jan. 1961; Freese, Ernst (Box 56)
  - Mutagenic and Inactivating DNA Alterations, Freese, Elisabeth Bautz; Freese, Ernst (Box 56)
  - On the Specificity of DNA Polymerase, n.d.; Freese, Elisabeth Bautz; Freese, Ernst (Box 56)
  - The Action of T2 Bacteriophage Ghosts on Escherichia Coli B, n.d.; French, R.C.; Siminovitch, Louis (Box 56)
  - The Reduction of Infective Centers by Blending when E. Coli is Infected by T2 in the Presence of Sodium Cyanide, Jun. 1958; Friedman, S. and S. Esrig (Box 56)
  - The Course of Infection with T-Even Phages on Mutants of E. Coli K-12 Defective in the Synthesis of Uridine Diphosphoglucose, n.d.; Fukasawa, Toshio; Saito, Shigeru (Box 57)
  - A Mutation in Escherichia Coli that Affects UDPG Pyrophosphorylase Activity and Galactose Fermentation, Fukasawa, Toshio, Kishiko Jokura, and Kyoshi Kurahashi; Fukasawa, Toshio; Jokura, Kishiko; Kurahashi, Kyoshi (Box 57)
  - Chronology of Viral Functions in Bacteriophage a, n.d.; Donini, P.; Gaeta, F.S.; Graziosi, F.; Veneziani-Brizi, L. (Box 57)
  - Rationality and Irrationality of Technology in Advanced Industrial Societies, 1970; Gallino, Luciano (Box 57)
  - Detection of Viruses by Chemical and Biologic Means (Box 57)
  - Selective Synthesis of T-Even Bacteriophage Early Messenger in Vitro, n.d.; Colvill, A.J.E.; Geiduschek, E.P.; Sarnat, M.; Snyder, L. (Box 57)
  - "Use of a Foreign Epitope as a Tag"" for the Localization of Minor Proteins within a Cell: The Case of the Immunity Protein to Colicin A""", [198-]; Baty, Daniel; Geli, Vincent; Lazdunski, Claude (Box 57)
  - Nalidixic Acid Resistance: A Second Genetic Character Involved in DNA Gyrase Activity, Gellert, Martin; Itoh, Tateo; Mizuuchi, Kiyoshi; O'Dea, Mary H.; Tomizawa, Jun-ichi (Box 57)
  - Comments on the Drug Abuse Problem, 1971; Goldstein, Avram (Box 57)
  - Next Moves in Escalating the War in Vietnam, 26 Aug. 1966; Goldstein, Walter (Box 57)
  - Phenotypic Masking and Streptomycin Dependence, [1967]; Gorini, Luigi (Box 57)
  - Suppression, 1966; Beckwith, Jonathan R.; Gorini, Luigi (Box 57)
  - Who Has Donned Lysenko's Mantle?, 1984; Gould, Stephen Jay (Box 57)
  - Biosynthetic Modifications Induced by DNA Animal Viruses, Green, Maurice (Box 57)
  - Regulation of Genetic Expression in Bacteriophage-Host Systems, n.d.; Green, Melvin H. (Box 57)
  - Pathology in Fields Collateral to Tissue Culture, [1956]; Greene, Harry S.N. (Box 57)
  - Psychological Dangers of Shelters, n.d.; Grinspoon, Lester (Box 57)
  - Contribution à l'Étude du Rôle de Différents Constituants Cellulaires dans la Biosynthèse des Protéines, Jun. 1962; Gros, François (Box 57)
  - "Protein Synthesis, Mitosis, and Differentiation", May-67; Gross, Paul R. (Box 57)
  - Lysis Inhibition. Induction of Lysis by Colicine, 1966; Guéron, Martine (Box 57)
  - Complementation between Amber Mutants of R17, Jun. 1966; Gussin, Gary Nathaniel (Box 57)
  - [Unidentified], n.d.; Guthrie, Edwin R. (Edwin Ray), 1886-1959 (Box 57)
  - The Myth of Ecological Doom, n.d.; Hagen, Everett E. (Box 58)
  - Ultrastructure of Virus-Induced Tumor Cells, Mar. 1960; Haguenau, François (Box 58)
  - Adaptive Evolution That Requires Multiple Spontaneous Mutations, 1988; Hall, Barry G. (Box 58)
  - Axonal Transport--Lecture, n.d.; Hall, Zach W. (Box 58)
  - Chemical Structure of Membranes--Lecture, 1971; Hall, Zach W. (Box 58)
  - Chemistry of Synaptic Transmission I--Lecture, n.d.; Hall, Zach W. (Box 58)
  - Chemistry of Synaptic Transmission II--Lecture, n.d.; Hall, Zach W. (Box 58)
  - Chemistry of Synaptic Transmission III--Lecture, n.d.; Hall, Zach W. (Box 58)
  - Sodium Transport--Lecture, n.d.; Hall, Zach W. (Box 58)
  - "Amphetamines and Marihuana, an Occasional Paper of the Salk Institute", [1970]; Hamburg, David A.; Melges, Frederick T.; Tinklenberg, Jared R. (Box 58)
  - Membranes and Energy: Transduction in Bacteria, Harold, Franklin M. (Box 58)
  - Methodology in Transduction, 1961; Hartman, Philip E. (Box 58)
  - The Functioning of T-Even Phages with Unglucosylated DNA in Restricting E. Coli Host Cells, n.d.; Hattman, Stanley (Box 58)
  - [Host-Induced Modification of T-Even Phages to the T* Form], Hattman, Stanley (Box 58)
  - "Purification and Characterization of the Unusual Deoxynucleoside a-N-(9-Beta-D-21-Deoxyribofuranosylpurin-6-yl) Glycinamide, Specified by the Phage Mu Modification Function", Crain, Pamela F.; Hattman, Stanley; Swinton, David (Box 58)
  - Evidence for Circular DNA Forms of a Bacterial Plasmid, n.d.; Helsinki, Donald R.; Roth, Thomas F. (Box 58)
  - Growth and Inheritance in Bacteriophage, 1952; Chase, Martha; Coon, Robert; Hershey, A. D., (Alfred Day), 1908- (Box 58)
  - Independent Functions of Viral Protein and Nucleic Acid in Growth of Bacteriophage, Chase, Martha; Hershey, A. D., (Alfred Day), 1908- (Box 58)
  - Some Central Problems of Viral Growth, n.d.; Hershey, A. D., (Alfred Day), 1908- (Box 58)
  - P1-Mediated Transduction in a Recombination Deficient Mutant, Hertman, Israel (Box 58)
  - "P1-Mediated Transduction of the rec"" Gene""", 1966; Hertman, Israel (Box 58)
  - Microbiology Qualifying Examination, 1961; Higa, Akiko (Box 58)
  - The Influence of Ultraviolet Irradiation on General Transduction in Pseudomonas Aeruginosa, 1960; Holloway, Bruce W.; Monk, Marilyn (Box 58)
  - Transduction in Pseudomonas Aeruginosa, [195-]; Holloway, Bruce W.; Monk, Marilyn (Box 58)
  - Viral Integration Near c-myc in 10-20% of MCF 247 Induced AKR Lymphomas, Hartley, Janet W.; Holland, Christie A.; Hopkins, Nancy Haven; Li, Yen (Box 58)
  - Replication of RNA Viruses. V. Template Activity of Synthetic Ribopolymers in the QBeta RNA Polymerase Reaction, n.d.; August, J.T.; Banerjee, A.K.; Eoyang, Lillian; Hori, K. (Box 58)
  - Galactokinase Formation by L-gal Prophage, n.d.; Horowitz (Box 58)
  - A Mutant of Bacteriophage T4 Defective in a-Glucosyl Transferase, 1967; Hosoda, Junko (Box 58)
  - Characterization of DNA by Biological Activity (Bacterial Transformation), n.d.; Hotchkiss, Rollin D. (Box 58)
  - Isolation of Sodium Deoxyribonucleate in Biologically Active Form from Bacteria, n.d.; Hotchkiss, Rollin D. (Box 58)
  - Isolation and Characterization of DNA Sequences Amplified in Multidrug Resistant Hamster Cells, Croop, James; Gros, Philippe; Housman, David E. (Box 58)
  - P-lkc X P-lvir, n.d.; Hsu, [ ] and Burns (Box 58)
  - Studies of Fractionated HeLa Cell Metaphase Chromosomes. I. The Chromosomal Distribution of DNA Complementary to 28s and 18s Ribosomal RNA and to Cytoplasmic Messenger RNA, Attardi, Giuseppe; Huberman, Joel A. (Box 58)
  - The Recovery of Man, n.d.; Hunt, John (Box 58)
  - Accumulation of Label from C14-Streptomycin by Escherichia Coli, [1961]; Hurwitz, Charles; Rosano, Carmen L. (Box 58)
  - Kinetics of Loss of Viability of Escherichia Coli Exposed to Streptomycin, n.d.; Hurwitz, Charles; Landau, J.V.; Rosano, Carmen L. (Box 58)
  - Requirement of a Streptomycin-Initiated Protein Synthesis for the Lethal Action of Streptomycin, [196-]; Hurwitz, Charles; Rosano, Carmen L. (Box 58)
  - Toward Syntax of the Genetic Code, n.d.; Inouye, Hiroshi (Box 59)
  - Biosynthesis and Assembly of the Outer Membrane Proteins of Escherichia Coli, Inouye, Masayori (Box 59)
  - The Synthesis and Structure of Normal and Abnormal Hemoglobins, Itano, Harvey A. (Box 59)
  - Chromosomal Alterations Affecting the Regulation of Histidine Biosynthetic Enzymes in Salmonella, n.d.; Ames, Bruce N.; Hartman, Philip E.; Jacob, François, 1920- (Box 59)
  - "Détermination de Liaisons Génétiques, Chez Escherichia Coli K12, à l'Aide de Radiophosphore", Jan. 1957; Fuerst, Clarence R.; Jacob, François, 1920-; Wollman, Elie (Box 59)
  - Elements of Regulatory Circuits in Bacteria, Sep. 1962; Jacob, François, 1920-; Monod, Jacques (Box 59)
  - Episomic Elements in Bacteria, 1960; Jacob, François, 1920-; Schaeffer, Pierre; Wollman, Elie (Box 59)
  - Étude Génétique d'un Bactériophage Tempéré d'Escherichia Coli, n.d.; Jacob, François, 1920-; Wollman, Elie (Box 59)
  - Gènes de Structure et Gènes de Régulation dans la Biosynthèse des Protéines, Jacob, François, 1920-; Monod, Jacques (Box 59)
  - "The Genetic Control and Cytoplasmic Expression of Inducibility"" in the Synthesis of Beta-Galactosidase by E. Coli""", [195-]; Jacob, François, 1920-; Monod, Jacques; Pardee, Arthur B. (Box 59)
  - Genetic Control of Viral Functions--Lecture, 18 Sep. 1958; Jacob, François, 1920- (Box 59)
  - On the Regulation of DNA Replication in Bacteria, n.d.; Brenner, Sydney; Cuzin, François; Jacob, François, 1920- (Box 59)
  - L'Opéron: Groupe de Gènes à Expression Coordonée par un Opérateur, n.d.; Jacob, François, 1920-; Monod, Jacques; Perrin, David; Sanchez, Carmen (Box 59)
  - Primitive Teratocarcinoma Cells Express a Differentiation Antigen Specified by a Gene at the T-Locus in the Mouse, n.d.; Artzt, Karen; Bennett, Dorothea; Jacob, François, 1920- (Box 59)
  - Transfer and Expression of Genetic Information in Escherichia Coli K12, Jun. 1958; Jacob, François, 1920- (Box 59)
  - Studies on Colicin E3 and Its Immunity Protein, Oct. 1974; Jakes, Karen Sorkin (Box 59)
  - Stretch Receptors and Control of Movements, Mar. 1971; Jansen, Jan (Box 59)
  - "Comparative Susceptibility of Tissue Culture Cells, Experimental Animals and Man", [1957]; Jervis, George A. (Box 59)
  - The Poxviruses, 1965; Joklik, Wolfgang K. (Box 59)
  - Beta-Galactosidase Transport in Bacterial Membrane Preparations: Energy Coupling Via Membrane-Bound D-Lactic Dehydrogenase, [1970]; Barnes, Eugene M., Jr.; Kaback, H. Ronald (Box 59)
  - The Electrochemical Gradient of Protons and Its Relationship to Active Transport in Escherichia Coli Membrane Vesicles, [1976]; Kaback, H. Ronald; Ramos, Sofia; Schuldiner, Shimon (Box 59)
  - The Relationship of a Membrane-Bound D-(-)-Lactic Dehydrogenase to Amino Acid Transport in Isolated Bacterial Membrane Preparations, Kaback, H. Ronald; Milner, L.S. (Box 59)
  - A Comparison of Galactose and Arabinose Utilization Systems in E. Coli, 24-May-63; Kaempfer, Raymond (Box 59)
  - Voltage-Dependent Channels Formed by Colicins, Jan. 1981; Kagan, Bruce Laurence (Box 59)
  - A Genetic Analysis of Bacteriophage Lambda, 1954; Kaiser, Armin Dale (Box 60)
  - "One-Eighth of a Century with the Massachusetts General Hospital as Biochem"" Chief""", [1974]; Kalckar, Herman M., (Herman Moritz), 1908-1991 (Box 60)
  - Origins of the Concept Oxidative Phosphorylation, 1973; Kalckar, Herman M., (Herman Moritz), 1908-1991 (Box 60)
  - Studies on Bacteria Made Thymine Deficient by Means of Sulfonamides, 1957; Kalle, G.P. (Box 60)
  - Studies on Genetic Recombinations among Mutants of Escherichia Coli, Jun. 1949; Kann, Ellen E. (Box 60)
  - Comparison of Susceptible and Resistant Cells to Infection with Poliomyelitis Virus, [1954]; Kaplan, Albert S. (Box 60)
  - Effect of Nucleoside Analogues on Cells Infected with Pseudorabies Virus, Dec. 1966; Ben-Porat, Tamar; Kaplan, Albert S. (Box 60)
  - The Herpes Viruses, n.d.; Kaplan, Albert S. (Box 60)
  - Studies on the Control of the Infective Process in Cells Infected with Pseudorabies Virus, Jun. 1966; Ben-Porat, Tamar; Coto, Celia; Kaplan, Albert S. (Box 60)
  - Experimental Alteration of Host Response to an Occult Tumor Virus: The Induction of Thymic Lymphosarcomas in X-Irradiated Mice, Mar. 1960; Kaplan, Henry S. (Box 60)
  - Some Implications of Indirect Induction Mechanisms in Carcinogenesis, Kaplan, Henry S. (Box 60)
  - Science and Social Values, 1970; Kaplan, Martin M. (Box 60)
  - Bibliography, [195-]; Kaudewitz, Fritz (Box 60)
  - Production of Bacterial Mutants with Nitrous Acid, 1959; Kaudewitz, Fritz (Box 60)
  - Biochemical Characterization of the 5B4 Antigen: A Membrane Glycoprotein Expressed at the Time of Neuronal Sprouting, n.d.; Ellis, Leland; Kayalar, Celik; Rosenberg, Jay; Troy, Frederic A. (Box 60)
  - Bound Nucleotides and Conformational Changes in Oxidative and Phosphorylation, Boyer, Paul D.; Kayalar, Celik; Rosing, Jan; Smith, Dan J. (Box 60)
  - Channel Properties of Colicin E1 in Liposomes, n.d.; Düzgünes, Nejat; Erdheim, G.R.; Kayalar, Celik (Box 60)
  - Characterization of a Factor Able to Repress Enzyme Synthesis in Escherichia Coli K12, Clark, Virginia L.; Fan, J.; Kayalar, Celik (Box 60)
  - Cloning and Identification of the Colicin E1 Immunity Gene, Goldman, Kenneth M.; Kastelein, Robert A.; Kayalar, Celik; Shanafelt, Armen B. (Box 60)
  - Cloning and Over-Expression of the Colicin E1 Immunity Gene, Goldman, Kenneth M.; Kastelein, Robert A.; Kayalar, Celik; Shanafelt, Armen B. (Box 60)
  - The Correlation between Fusion and the Developmental Regulation of Membrane Glycoproteins in L6 Myoblasts, Ellis, Leland; Kayalar, Celik; Rosenberg, Jay; Troy, Frederic A. (Box 60)
  - Determination of the Molecularity of the Colicin E1 Channel by Stopped-Flow Ion Flux Kinetics, [1985]; Bruggemann, Edward P.; Kayalar, Celik (Box 60)
  - Identification of the Plasmid-Encoded Immunity Protein for Colicin E1 in the Inner Membrane of Escherichia Coli, n.d.; Goldman, Kenneth M.; Kayalar, Celik; Suit, Joan L. (Box 60)
  - Kinetic and Exchange Reaction Probes of the Mechanism of ATP Synthesis, Boyer, Paul D.; Kayalar, Celik; Rosing, Jan (Box 60)
  - Membrane Action of Colicin E1: Detection by the Release of Carboxyfluorescein and Calsein from Liposomes, Düzgünes, Nejat; Kayalar, Celik (Box 60)
  - A Model for Proton Translocation in Biomembranes Based on Keto-Enol Shifts in Hydrogen Bonded Peptide Groups, [1978]; Kayalar, Celik (Box 60)
  - Nature of Energy-Input in ATP Synthesis, n.d.; Boyer, Paul D.; Kayalar, Celik; Rosing, Jan (Box 60)
  - Probes of Energy Input in ATP Formation by Oxidative Phosphorylation, [197-]; Boyer, Paul D.; Kayalar, Celik; Rosing, Jan (Box 60)
  - On the Emergence of Cognitive Neuroscience, [1980]; Kean, Mary-Louise; Nadel, Lynn (Box 60)
  - Anwendung einer Neuen Methode auf das Quantitative Studium von Bakterienlysaten im Elektronen-Mikroskop, Kellenberger, Eduard (Box 60)
  - Einleitung, n.d.; Arber, Werner; Kellenberger, Eduard; Kellenberger, Grete (Box 60)
  - Functions and Properties Related to the Tail Fibers of Bacteriophage T4, 1965; Bolle, A.; Boy de la Tour, E.; Kellenberger, Eduard (Box 60)
  - Precise Measures of the Mean Weight of Individual Particles of Polystyrene Latex 15 N-7, 1959; Kellenberger, Eduard (Box 60)
  - [A Study of Hybrids between Two Distantly Related Strains of Escherichia Coli], n.d.; Kellenberger, Eduard; Lieb, M.; Weigle, Jean J. (Box 60)
  - Untersuchung der Struktur des Bakteriophagen T2 mit Hilfe von Oxydativem Abbau, n.d.; Arber, Werner; Kellenberger, Eduard (Box 60)
  - A Host Mutation Causing the Production of Colicin E1 to be Temperature-Sensitive, n.d.; Kennedy, Christina K. (Box 61)
  - Induction of Colicin Production by High Temperature or Inhibition of Protein Synthesis, Kennedy, Christina K. (Box 61)
  - Isolation and Characterization of a Mutant Colicin E2, Kennedy, Christina K.; Sodergren, Erica (Box 61)
  - Isolation of a Mutant Colicin E2, n.d.; Kennedy, Christina K.; Kleinman, S.H. (Box 61)
  - Production of Colicin E1 or E2 Induced by High Temperatures or Blocks in Protein Synthesis--Abstracts, Kennedy, Christina K. (Box 61)
  - Molecular Aspects of Circadian Systems, n.d.; Hastings, J. Woodland; Keynan, Alexander (Box 61)
  - Resporulation of Outgrowing Bacillus Subtilis Spores, n.d.; Berns, A.A.; Dunn, G.; Keynan, Alexander; Mandelstam, J.; Young, M. (Box 61)
  - Stages in Germination of Spores of Bacillus Licheniformis, [1962]; Halmann, M.; Keynan, Alexander (Box 61)
  - Protein Synthesis and the Formation of Messenger RNA in the Course of Phage Infection, Gorlenko, Zh. M.; Khesin, R.B.; Shemyakin, M.F. (Box 61)
  - RNA Polymerase in Escherichia Coli B Infected with T2 Phage, 1962; Gorlenko, Zh. M.; Khesin, R.B.; Shemyakin, M.F. (Box 61)
  - Comparative Susceptibility of Roller Tube Cultures of Different Tissues to Poliomyelitis Viruses, [1957]; Kiboick, Sidney (Box 61)
  - Anticarcinogenesis, Jun. 1960; Kinosita, Riojun (Box 61)
  - The Kinetics of RNA and Protein Formation in Salmonella Typhimurium During the Transition Between Different States of Balanced Growth, Kjeldgaard, Niels Ole (Box 61)
  - Somatic Cell Genetics, n.d.; Klein, George (Box 61)
  - Drug Resistance of Enteric Bacteria. VI. Introduction of Bacteriophage P1 CM into S. Typhi and Formation of P1 dCM and F-CM Element, Kondo, Eiko; Mitsuhashi, Susumu (Box 61)
  - Colicins and Other Bacteriocins with Established Modes of Action, 1982; Konisky, Jordan (Box 61)
  - A Consideration of Virus-Host Relationships in Neoplasia at the Level of the Whole Animal, n.d.; Koprowski, Hilary (Box 61)
  - The Rate of Synthesis of Deoxyribonucleic Acid in E. Coli B. Infected with T2r+ Bacteriophage, [1956]; Kozloff, Lloyd M.; Vidaver, George A. (Box 61)
  - Fluorescent Probes for the Energized State in Biological Membranes, n.d.; Brocklehurst, John R.; Kraayenhof, Ruud; Lee, Chuan-Pu (Box 61)
  - A Study of Gene Action in Ultraviolet-Irradiated Bacteriophage, 1957; Krieg, David R. (Box 61)
  - Current Concepts of Icosohedral RNA Biosynthesis, 24-May-63; Kurzrock, Sheila (Box 61)